sixent.com 2010-06-20

# SIXENT PRIVACY POLICY

Ramius Corporation ("Ramius"), the developer and operator of Sixent, is absolutely committed to protecting the privacy of our users' personal information. The following statement explains our information gathering and dissemination practices.

## Information Collected

When you register with Sixent, or enter via a Single Sign On process, Sixent requires a minimum disclosure of your first name, last name and email address. Some organizations may also require you to disclose your date of birth and gender. Collectively this is all referred to as "registration data". You also have the option to disclose in one or multiple personal profiles your address, phone number, gender, and other optional profile information not required to register. As part of your registration, you will be asked to select a user name and password for use at Sixent. Please keep your password confidential at all times. If you believe that the security of your password has been compromised, please contact Ramius immediately.

Ramius does not monitor your communications on Sixent, but may, in its discretion, do so if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of Ramius or others, or to protect the personal safety of other Users or the public, or to address any contravention of the Terms of Service which governs your use of this service.

## Use of Information

The registration data - including your first and last names, user name, and email address - is used by our service to identify you and your contributions to the Sixent system. A valid email address is required by our service to provide you with updated information from Sixent, including activity updates, requested search results, invitations, and service information. You may limit disclosure of your registration data throughout the system by selecting options within your profile.

Demographic and profile data is used to personalize our service to your interests and to deliver personalized information to you. Demographic and profile data may be shared with partners such as investors and advertisers on an _aggregate_ basis only. Ramius does not disclose personally identifiable information specific to any of our members.

## Use of Cookies

A cookie is a file that is written to your computer when you access certain web pages. We use cookies to personalize our service to your interests and to ensure data security. Upon logging in or entering Sixent, cookies are set to authorize you during your visit of the Sixent site ("session"). All cookies will expire when you close your browser or turn off your computer. Data stored in cookies is encrypted to prevent tampering. Cookies identify you as you navigate the system to ensure all rights and permissions are respected.

## Log Files

Logs of website traffic are collected and include information such as IP addresses, browser types and cookie information. This information is collected to analyze trends, administer the site and to calculate overall activity. Personally identifiable traffic patterns are not disclosed to third parties.

## Public Information

Within Sixent, you have the option of allowing any of your information or content to be open to the public. Please remember that any information or content disclosed as such becomes public information and you should exercise caution in disclosing as such.

## Security

This website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of information and content placed on the Sixent site. The information and content is stored in a secure operating environment that cannot be accessed by unauthorized parties.

## Other Websites' Links

This website contains links to other websites. Ramius is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

## Opt-Out, Delete/Deactivate

Activity updates (an email sent to you summarizing the activities within your profiles) may be deactivated by at any time by selecting "My Setup" from the main Dashboard page, followed by "My Preferences", and then selecting "Never send me the summary" under the "Activity Summary Email" heading. setting "Activity Updates".

You also have the option of turning off other communications from Sixent by selecting "My Setup" from the main Dashboard page, followed by "My Preferences", and then deselecting various options under "Email Notifications".

Users can set the amount of personal information they reveal in each profile, page or group on an individual basis by changing the "Page Visibility and Permissions" options for each page or "Pod Visibility" options for each Pod.

The monthly Sixent newsletter contains an "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email. Following this link instantly removed the user from the newsletter mailing list.

## Correct/Update

Sixent allows users the option to change all information previously provided. To make changes to registration data, select "My Setup" from the main Dashboard page, followed by "My Account", where you can proceed to make the required changes.

## Privacy Policy Changes

If we should change the Sixent privacy policy, we will post those changes prominently on our website so that users will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If we ever change the way we collect or use personally identifiable information, we will e-mail our users noting the change and give our users the option to opt-out of such a change.

## Contacting Ramius Corporation / CommunityZero

Should you have any questions or comments regarding this Sixent privacy policy, or the practices of this website, you may contact us [here](http://help.sixent.com/index.php?departmentid=4&&_m=tickets&_a=submit&step=1), or write to us here:

Ramius Corporation  
Suite 480, 47 Clarence Street  
Ottawa, ON K1N 9K1  
Canada 

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
